[
  {
    "id": "7270aef9-4ca7-4ec9-b440-87f5ec255a0b",
    "name": "Spanish",
    "flashcards": {
      "23e3c332-a3c0-4e6b-9190-96e097ca1334": {
        "id": "23e3c332-a3c0-4e6b-9190-96e097ca1334",
        "front": "hola",
        "back": "hello"
      },
      "fc59255d-7d6b-4f37-b19e-d93717ed3b54": {
        "id": "fc59255d-7d6b-4f37-b19e-d93717ed3b54",
        "front": "adiós",
        "back": "goodbye"
      },
      "fe4dd5d0-ca0d-4424-9c65-d740c5c53fc1": {
        "id": "fe4dd5d0-ca0d-4424-9c65-d740c5c53fc1",
        "front": "gracias",
        "back": "thank you"
      },
      "b8ac8ec8-a1a4-41a4-b3c7-4165258ad05d": {
        "id": "b8ac8ec8-a1a4-41a4-b3c7-4165258ad05d",
        "front": "por favor",
        "back": "please"
      },
      "a1fe6cf1-127c-4248-b7d2-2380ef89b522": {
        "id": "a1fe6cf1-127c-4248-b7d2-2380ef89b522",
        "front": "sí",
        "back": "yes"
      },
      "8bdf931e-13f2-477f-9909-3f9c9167c24c": {
        "id": "8bdf931e-13f2-477f-9909-3f9c9167c24c",
        "front": "no",
        "back": "no"
      },
      "22379f0c-848e-444a-8bf9-0f243789eb6b": {
        "id": "22379f0c-848e-444a-8bf9-0f243789eb6b",
        "front": "buenos días",
        "back": "good morning"
      },
      "aba8fb2d-60b8-40d9-ac34-07265b0cf5fd": {
        "id": "aba8fb2d-60b8-40d9-ac34-07265b0cf5fd",
        "front": "buenas tardes",
        "back": "good afternoon"
      },
      "3c8ceaa0-2b96-4e54-b7c5-ed38339f9ff9": {
        "id": "3c8ceaa0-2b96-4e54-b7c5-ed38339f9ff9",
        "front": "buenas noches",
        "back": "good evening"
      },
      "1e00931e-5d40-4282-8521-b5c2e5f04c97": {
        "id": "1e00931e-5d40-4282-8521-b5c2e5f04c97",
        "front": "hasta luego",
        "back": "see you later"
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "d8ceac0d-a8f0-4336-930c-5fff865655bb",
    "name": "German",
    "flashcards": {
      "264de03b-e444-4595-986d-8c10700adb4e": {
        "id": "264de03b-e444-4595-986d-8c10700adb4e",
        "front": "house",
        "back": "Haus"
      },
      "f1413174-30bd-48c0-ac3c-8e1ee9280641": {
        "id": "f1413174-30bd-48c0-ac3c-8e1ee9280641",
        "front": "car",
        "back": "Auto"
      },
      "9c4c3ede-bd8a-44b6-acb3-13b57e9a7a28": {
        "id": "9c4c3ede-bd8a-44b6-acb3-13b57e9a7a28",
        "front": "book",
        "back": "Buch"
      },
      "89bb665f-1426-49e4-94d0-4bd206772338": {
        "id": "89bb665f-1426-49e4-94d0-4bd206772338",
        "front": "computer",
        "back": "Computer"
      },
      "ba596230-e55a-4ac1-9734-c2c133c924c8": {
        "id": "ba596230-e55a-4ac1-9734-c2c133c924c8",
        "front": "dog",
        "back": "Hund"
      },
      "0928712c-9063-442a-b66f-a2e6b8754481": {
        "id": "0928712c-9063-442a-b66f-a2e6b8754481",
        "front": "cat",
        "back": "Katze"
      },
      "9392121f-a433-4ce8-a9bf-caf2eb54b295": {
        "id": "9392121f-a433-4ce8-a9bf-caf2eb54b295",
        "front": "tree",
        "back": "Baum"
      },
      "9b900b7e-a906-4e7c-b1dd-aad910d87f1b": {
        "id": "9b900b7e-a906-4e7c-b1dd-aad910d87f1b",
        "front": "sun",
        "back": "Sonne"
      },
      "59ee5602-c862-4e94-a226-3a64a7ce9af6": {
        "id": "59ee5602-c862-4e94-a226-3a64a7ce9af6",
        "front": "moon",
        "back": "Mond"
      },
      "407beda5-f6db-40ab-93cd-806063c7068c": {
        "id": "407beda5-f6db-40ab-93cd-806063c7068c",
        "front": "water",
        "back": "Wasser"
      },
      "c344e879-6324-4518-ab9d-db5f71af104a": {
        "id": "c344e879-6324-4518-ab9d-db5f71af104a",
        "front": "fire",
        "back": "Feuer"
      },
      "0c3c9152-9ec3-488c-b8cf-ff5a8d45d048": {
        "id": "0c3c9152-9ec3-488c-b8cf-ff5a8d45d048",
        "front": "earth",
        "back": "Erde"
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "7e2ad96f-cd00-4183-b4b8-b3dfbb25c71a",
    "name": "Italian",
    "flashcards": {
      "ce0c287b-ae11-4882-9bf5-da5b929a5bf6": {
        "id": "ce0c287b-ae11-4882-9bf5-da5b929a5bf6",
        "front": "hello",
        "back": "ciao"
      },
      "f0dbf803-05a3-4833-974d-a9df362ba8f6": {
        "id": "f0dbf803-05a3-4833-974d-a9df362ba8f6",
        "front": "goodbye",
        "back": "arrivederci"
      },
      "b41e72d9-6f0b-46e4-be0b-d84ac23277cc": {
        "id": "b41e72d9-6f0b-46e4-be0b-d84ac23277cc",
        "front": "thank you",
        "back": "grazie"
      },
      "1231decc-d909-4961-ba3d-c42e9f7cf86b": {
        "id": "1231decc-d909-4961-ba3d-c42e9f7cf86b",
        "front": "please",
        "back": "per favore"
      },
      "2f6c9172-95bd-4d5a-a9c6-c65d2e12f4e2": {
        "id": "2f6c9172-95bd-4d5a-a9c6-c65d2e12f4e2",
        "front": "yes",
        "back": "sì"
      },
      "2268ee50-d989-4ea0-a5b4-ed05cbba6e43": {
        "id": "2268ee50-d989-4ea0-a5b4-ed05cbba6e43",
        "front": "no",
        "back": "no"
      },
      "6097d29c-ca8a-4008-8a32-3900540ff1c2": {
        "id": "6097d29c-ca8a-4008-8a32-3900540ff1c2",
        "front": "good morning",
        "back": "buongiorno"
      },
      "3764a68f-9a87-4850-a1c8-8049e88006e3": {
        "id": "3764a68f-9a87-4850-a1c8-8049e88006e3",
        "front": "good afternoon",
        "back": "buon pomeriggio"
      },
      "5b21e88d-55c5-4777-aeb5-db4cce62fbc9": {
        "id": "5b21e88d-55c5-4777-aeb5-db4cce62fbc9",
        "front": "good evening",
        "back": "buona sera"
      },
      "51361492-a50b-4678-a181-7586d7964def": {
        "id": "51361492-a50b-4678-a181-7586d7964def",
        "front": "see you later",
        "back": "ci vediamo dopo"
      },
      "bf3cce1a-588e-49cc-bbba-4274e6d0f32d": {
        "id": "bf3cce1a-588e-49cc-bbba-4274e6d0f32d",
        "front": "car",
        "back": "macchina"
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "4df08bae-db27-4abd-8c1e-64a030b76d49",
    "name": "French",
    "flashcards": {
      "34a72b0f-fbe4-4ae1-a593-b42b133292ca": {
        "id": "34a72b0f-fbe4-4ae1-a593-b42b133292ca",
        "front": "hello",
        "back": "bonjour"
      },
      "7927d324-16cd-484f-a82a-1236fbdd704a": {
        "id": "7927d324-16cd-484f-a82a-1236fbdd704a",
        "front": "goodbye",
        "back": "au revoir"
      },
      "20c6dfe8-3c81-4f56-a2f2-f9644644d296": {
        "id": "20c6dfe8-3c81-4f56-a2f2-f9644644d296",
        "front": "thank you",
        "back": "merci"
      },
      "f6886d59-defd-4f7a-9d4c-58945cbf5ee8": {
        "id": "f6886d59-defd-4f7a-9d4c-58945cbf5ee8",
        "front": "please",
        "back": "s'il vous plaît"
      },
      "e7ed752e-7137-4499-84f7-5c6cfe50a1da": {
        "id": "e7ed752e-7137-4499-84f7-5c6cfe50a1da",
        "front": "yes",
        "back": "oui"
      },
      "a64db3ff-c044-4eaa-8cdc-f8b59fa8cc51": {
        "id": "a64db3ff-c044-4eaa-8cdc-f8b59fa8cc51",
        "front": "no",
        "back": "non"
      },
      "d487b535-3934-4d56-904f-6d55fb874960": {
        "id": "d487b535-3934-4d56-904f-6d55fb874960",
        "front": "good morning",
        "back": "bonjour"
      },
      "b7c2c11e-bcc7-4d50-b4a8-4c6ac5c0b551": {
        "id": "b7c2c11e-bcc7-4d50-b4a8-4c6ac5c0b551",
        "front": "good afternoon",
        "back": "bon après-midi"
      },
      "7332fa5c-8b98-4fa9-aa9e-eadbb26f57ee": {
        "id": "7332fa5c-8b98-4fa9-aa9e-eadbb26f57ee",
        "front": "good evening",
        "back": "bonsoir"
      },
      "c4f19cc8-7fcc-44bb-9677-37899e1690fb": {
        "id": "c4f19cc8-7fcc-44bb-9677-37899e1690fb",
        "front": "see you later",
        "back": "à plus tard"
      },
      "d8850155-5dcd-48f4-affd-7826aa189dbf": {
        "id": "d8850155-5dcd-48f4-affd-7826aa189dbf",
        "front": "car",
        "back": "voiture"
      },
      "4203b599-2654-4cc9-b42d-5e7d5803380b": {
        "id": "4203b599-2654-4cc9-b42d-5e7d5803380b",
        "front": "train",
        "back": "train"
      },
      "7c47d693-9d81-4c08-bd06-f7cab1519de7": {
        "id": "7c47d693-9d81-4c08-bd06-f7cab1519de7",
        "front": "bus",
        "back": "bus"
      },
      "c6dfb3af-e1eb-436d-b89f-3cd121ec823f": {
        "id": "c6dfb3af-e1eb-436d-b89f-3cd121ec823f",
        "front": "bicycle",
        "back": "vélo"
      },
      "f2fc2998-3fc4-4ea1-bd4a-4c0497738515": {
        "id": "f2fc2998-3fc4-4ea1-bd4a-4c0497738515",
        "front": "motorcycle",
        "back": "moto"
      },
      "901cb39f-a74f-4c5d-9bc7-49d8b0c0eb8d": {
        "id": "901cb39f-a74f-4c5d-9bc7-49d8b0c0eb8d",
        "front": "boat",
        "back": "bateau"
      },
      "dfa7bbc6-ee37-4993-a920-c8ce55af0a58": {
        "id": "dfa7bbc6-ee37-4993-a920-c8ce55af0a58",
        "front": "airplane",
        "back": "avion"
      },
      "c630c9b1-d094-4239-93b1-8d46943bed9a": {
        "id": "c630c9b1-d094-4239-93b1-8d46943bed9a",
        "front": "hotel",
        "back": "hôtel"
      },
      "c664579f-f837-4b13-b9f3-b74e436d714f": {
        "id": "c664579f-f837-4b13-b9f3-b74e436d714f",
        "front": "restaurant",
        "back": "restaurant"
      },
      "6d488ba2-81db-4365-949b-e2277fa4ec4e": {
        "id": "6d488ba2-81db-4365-949b-e2277fa4ec4e",
        "front": "coffee",
        "back": "café"
      },
      "115749c9-033c-471d-91ec-80b48e8cbeba": {
        "id": "115749c9-033c-471d-91ec-80b48e8cbeba",
        "front": "wine",
        "back": "vin"
      }
    }
  }
]